// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the little mouse?",
    answer: "Mira",
    options: [
      "Suzan",
      "Pretty",
      "Mira",
      "Marcia"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who gave her the name Mira?",
    answer: "Her grandmother",
    options: [
      "Her mother",
      "Her grandmother",
      "Her father",
      "Her grandfather"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What did her parents buy her as a birthday present?",
    answer: "A bicycle",
    options: [
      "A skateboard",
      "A telescope",
      "A bicycle",
      "A doll"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What did the bicycle come with?",
    answer: "Safety wear",
    options: [
      "A sun hat",
      "Sun glasses",
      "Boots",
      "Safety wear"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What was the safety wear that came with the bicycle?",
    answer: "A Helmet together with elbow and knee-pads",
    options: [
      "A jumpsuit for riders",
      "A Helmet together with elbow and knee-pads",
      "A jersey",
      "Boots and gloves"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Did Mira use or wear the safetywear?",
    answer: "No she did not",
    options: [
      "Yes she did",
      "Yes because knew it was important",
      "No she did not",
      "Yes she listened to her parents"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Why did Mira fall off her bicycle?",
    answer: "She tripped over a small rock on the road",
    options: [
      "She was trying dangerous stunts",
      "She did not know how to ride a bicycle",
      "The bicycle went really fast and she lost control",
      "She tripped over a small rock on the road"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Was Mira going to be injured as much, if she was wearing her safety wear?",
    answer: "No, the injuries would be less",
    options: [
      "Yes very bad",
      "No, the injuries would be less",
      "Yes it does not matter if she was wearing safetywear or not",
      "Yes because she fell to hard"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Did she enjoy spending lots of time at the hospital?",
    answer: "Not at all, she regreted not listening to her parents",
    options: [
      "She had a great time at the hospital",
      "She was given free candy at the hospital",
      "Yes toomuch",
      "Not at all, she regreted not listening to her parents"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the lesson Mira learned on this story?",
    answer: "We should always listen to our parents and play safe all the time",
    options: [
      "We should always do as we wish and do what we want",
      "Safety makes playing less fun",
      "We should not listen to our parents and not play safe all the time",
      "We should always listen to our parents and play safe all the time"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
